# delan@azabani.com

3359 F6FA AED9 B627 E700 F58E FC18 AA5D 1313 1313

www.azabani.com

#### delan on Bitbucket and GitHub

@dazabani

## **2017** (current)

# Software developer at Atlassian

Developing the self-hosted version of Jira Service Desk.

Cut build times on our main repository by 20%. Responsible for the JSD release process since August 2018, including the Early Access Program for Jira 8. Wrote and maintained the bulk of our documentation for our new starters and our builds and releases. Wrote an incremental build system for Maven using Python and POSIX shell that tracks successful build inputs with its own Git repository.

Gained a wide range of full-stack experience, using Java and Scala with OSGi and Spring on the back-end, ECMAScript and Backbone on the front-end, Groovy and Bamboo for continuous integration, and a heterogeneous persistence layer that supports five database systems through OFBiz, Active Objects, and Querydsl.

#### 2014 to 2016

# Casual academic at Curtin University

Tutored classes for Unix and C programming, operating systems, and first and second year software engineering, marked assignments and tests, wrote assessment revision material, and delivered it to more than a hundred students in a semester.

#### 2009 to 2010

# Software developer at Willetton Senior High School

Built and maintained web applications using PHP and MySQL, to enable staff to allocate classrooms, buses, and other facilities, and to allow English students to review texts that they have studied.

# Referees

+61 419 043 926 Nigel Dutton — computer science teacher, systems administrator,

and manager of operations at Willetton Senior High School

# Education

2013 to 2016 Bachelor of Science (Computer Science)

Curtin University (84.73 percent average)

2008 to 2012 Western Australian Certificate of Education

Willetton Senior High School (98.85 percentile)

# Awards and achievements

2015	ACS Foundation ICT Scholarship (Diamond Cyber)	
2014	Commendation from Curtin Science (2014 semester 2)	
2014	Curtin Vice-Chancellor's List (2013 semester 2 — top $1\%$ )	
2013	Commendation from Curtin Science (2013 semester 2)	
2013	Commendation from Curtin Computing (2013 semester 1)	
2012	Curtin Science Excellence Scholarship (96 percentile)	
2012	Distinction in WACE Computer Science (second best in WA)	
2011 to 2012	First prize in the MAWA Have Sum Fun competition (twice)	
2011 to 2012	Top student in WACE Computer Science (four times)	
2009 to 2012	Bronze in the Australian Informatics Olympiad (four times)	
2009 to 2010	Distinction in the Australian Mathematics Competition (twice)	
2008	High distinction in the Australian Mathematics Competition	
2007	Dux of Rostrata Primary School	

# Community involvement

2016	President	of	ComSSA

2013 to 2016 Committee member at ComSSA

Organised events, operated services, formalised processes, maintained correspondence, and liaised with sponsors and staff, for the computer science society at Curtin University. ComSSA runs social events and industry conventions, provides academic assistance, and represents computing, networking, and security students.

2014 Mentor at CoderDojo WA

Trained and supported school students aged 7–17 who are learning programming skills, with the use of Scratch, Python, Ruby, and more, at the weekly CoderDojo workshops at Curtin University.

2014 Engineering outreach volunteer at Curtin University

Demonstrated introductory programming skills using the Raspberry Pi computer, to eleven groups of high school students from years nine to twelve, with members of Engineers Without Borders Australia.

# **Employment history**

# 2017 (current)

## Software developer at Atlassian

Developing the self-hosted version of Jira Service Desk.

Cut build times on our main repository by 20%. Responsible for the JSD release process since August 2018, including the Early Access Program for Jira 8. Wrote and maintained the bulk of our documentation for our new starters and our builds and releases. Wrote an incremental build system for Maven using Python and POSIX shell that tracks successful build inputs with its own Git repository.

Gained a wide range of full-stack experience, using Java and Scala with OSGi and Spring on the back-end, ECMAScript and Backbone on the front-end, Groovy and Bamboo for continuous integration, and a heterogeneous persistence layer that supports five database systems through OFBiz, Active Objects, and Querydsl.

#### 2015

# Research intern at Pawsey Supercomputing Centre

Developed tools to allow content creators to easily arrange 3D scenes with models of the recently discovered wrecks of HMAS Sydney (II) and HSK Kormoran, animate these scenes, and render them on the Magnus supercomputer near Curtin University.

#### 2015

## **Technical operator** at Diamond Cyber

Improved the security of the organisation's public website, investigated secure communications platforms for penetration testing, and built a workstation for training new employees.

#### 2014

## Junior web developer at Aspermont Limited

Supported and maintained a legacy content management system that uses ASP, VBScript, and Microsoft SQL Server, and aided with the migration of applications to Amazon Web Services and ASP.NET.

#### 2014 to 2016

#### Casual academic at Curtin University

Tutored classes for Unix and C programming, operating systems, and first and second year software engineering, marked assignments and tests, wrote assessment revision material, and delivered it to more than a hundred students in a semester.

## 2009 to 2010

#### Software developer at Willetton Senior High School

Built and maintained web applications using PHP and MySQL, to enable staff to allocate classrooms, buses, and other facilities, and to allow English students to review texts that they have studied.